http://www.promat.co.uk/en-gb/about-us/corporate-policies/privacy-policy

Introduction
This Privacy Notice is designed to inform you about the personal data relating to you which Etex Building Performance Ltd, with registered office at Gordano House, Marsh Lane, Easton in Gordano, Bristol, BS20 0NE and registered in England and Wales under number 02163844, (acting as data controller and hereinafter referred as “We”, “Our” and “Us”) collects via the website Etex Building Performance (www.etex-bp.co.uk, www.siniat.co.uk, www.promat-direct.co.uk, or www.promat.co.uk ). (referred to hereinafter as the “Website”), why we collect and process such personal data, on which legal basis, and how we will handle personal data you provide us with and personal data we learn about you from your visit to the Website. Your use of the Website implies your acknowledgment of this Privacy Notice.
Legal basis
We process your personal data on the basis of your specific consent or on the basis of a legitimate interest which we believe you would be interested in following your previous delivery of our goods and services.
Whenever the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw such consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of such processing before the withdrawal of consent.
Personal data collected
We collect personal data relating to you (referred to hereinafter as “Personal Data”) in two ways:
through registration and sending of information that you choose to enter on certain pages of the Website. The information marked with the “*” symbol must be provided, to enable Us to fulfil the processing purposes, as mentioned below. Such Personal Data directly collected from you include your first and last name, personal or professional address, personal or professional email address, personal or professional mobile or other phone number, activity, position, title, message, or other personal information or contact information you provide Us with. We may also ask for your comments, suggestions, or other information relating to the Website, Our products or services, or Our company. Other specific types of information may be requested in connection with, other promotional offers or other marketing activities, including uploading text, video or audio content.
through cookies. For more information about cookies, please see below.
Use of Personal Data
Your Personal Data will exclusively be used to the extent necessary to allow Us:
To respond to your direct request, as described at the time when We collect your Personal Data or as otherwise described to you prior to the use of your Personal Data For example
Enquire for further information;
Distribute requested reference materials;
Provide you with services that you request; and
To manage your use of the Website, including to the extent applicable, your participation to promotional offers or other marketing and
to send you mailings or other marketing information about a selection of Our brands, affiliates and/or partners with whom We are conducting joint promotions or programs in which you may be interested through email/mail/text messaging (provided you have given Us, Our affiliates and/or partners the explicit prior consent to do so, where required under applicable law)
Make this website available to you and to provide you with content which is tailored to your individual tastes (e.g. to register for certain areas of the site);
Where you have given us your consent, to contact you (including by SMS and email) with products and services which we think may interest you.
We may combine the Personal Data you submit with other personal data we have obtained about you for the same purposes from other sources, including if you have provided your information to Us in other places or through another medium (such as social media platforms). These sources include:
Glenigan
LinkedIn
Events and Exhibitions
Facebook
Purchased mailing lists from reputable market research companies
We may not use your Personal Data for new purposes which are as yet unforeseen in this Privacy Notice except on the basis of an applicable statutory permission. In any event, prior to using Personal Data for other purposes, We will inform you about such change to this Privacy Notice. In case of consent-based activities, We will not process your Personal Data for such new purposes without first obtaining your consent.
Special category of personal data
We will not collect or process any special category of personal data relating to you. The special categories of Personal Data include data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or other beliefs of a similar nature, trade union membership, genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, health, sex life or sexual orientation.
Direct marketing
We will not use your Personal Data for electronic direct marketing purposes without your explicit prior consent, except where authorised under applicable law.
If at any time you decide not to receive any commercial or promotional information from Us, You may, free of charge and without having to provide any justification, opt-out of any direct marketing campaigns and oppose to the future processing of your Personal Data for such purposes by sending Us an email at marketing@etexbp.co.uk and mention “opt-out” in the subject of your email. Alternatively, you may use the opt-out procedure provided in any promotional message you receive from Us.
Please note that opting out from receiving promotional messages from Us will not prevent you from receiving information that relates to any contract you may have entered into with Us.
Surveys
From time to time we will conduct surveys to establish information to assist us in gaining your direct thoughts and opinions on our products, systems (Facebook, Linked In, Websites etc) and services.
Each Survey will invite you to participate; this will be classed asking for your consent to participate; your information gathered at the time of the survey will be only used for that purpose of the survey and will not assume consent for any other purpose.  Where fulfilment companies are used for the specific survey these will be specified in the Survey’s purpose statement.
Details of the purpose and scope of the Survey will be made clear for each Survey we may ask you to participate in, this will provide you with the details for you to clearly decide if you want to consent to participate in the Survey.
Personal data collected during the survey will be deleted upon the completion of the survey analysis and will not be stored or used for any other purpose.  Each Survey will request your consent each time you participate.
Participation in our surveys will not impact or influence any future buying or mailing preferences in the future and unless otherwise stated your participation will be anonymous.
Automated decision-making
We will not make use of automated decision-making processes, including profiling, except where authorised under applicable law. In such case we would inform you about the logic involved in the decision, as well as the significance and the envisaged consequences of such processing for you.
Sharing Personal Data and transferring Personal Data to third parties
We will not make your Personal Data available to any third party and shall not publicly disclose the Personal Data unless such transfers are based on your specific consent, necessary for the performance of a contract entered into between you and Us, or when such transfer of Personal Data is otherwise authorised or compulsory by law or by order of an administration or judicial authority.
We transfer your Personal Data to the following recipients:
ESM Branding for postal methods of communication.
Camargue PR for public relations
Please note that whenever your Personal Data are transferred to processors or third parties located outside the European Economic Area in countries which are not considered by the European Commission to guarantee an adequate level of personal data protection, We will ensure that appropriate measures are implemented according to the applicable national and European legislation relating to data protection. You may obtain a copy of the appropriate safeguards taken or information as to where they have been made available by sending Us an email at marketing@etex-bp.co.uk.
Use of cookies
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or other device by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the website.
General information about the cookies used
This Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our websites.
This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our websites and also allows us to improve our websites.
For detailed information on the cookies and other similar technologies that we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy. When you visit our Website for the first time, the entry page will show information on privacy and respective wording regarding the consent to the use of cookies through a “cookie banner”. If you continue to actively use the Website and do not actively object to the use of cookies, you agree to our use of cookies and such consent will be stored in your browser, so that the information does not have to be repeated on every page of the Website. Should the consent be missing in your browser (e.g. if you deleted your cookies), the “cookie banner” with privacy information will appear again the next time you visit the Website. We may install and use certain technically required cookies which therefore do not require your prior consent. We may also use session cookies which are automatically deleted at the end of your session and which also do not require your prior consent. Other cookies (such as cookies to improve the navigational experience by keeping record of certain data – this avoids you having to reintroduce such data at each connection – and by tailoring the content of the Website to your preferences) may be installed and used on the basis of your consent. You will find all relevant information about the cookies used by this Website in the table below.
Cookie name
Category of information stored
Purpose
Domain
Type of cookie
Retention time
Related to user tracking
Communication to 1/3 party
lang
Set by Linkedin when a page contains an embedded “Follow us” Panel.
www.promat.co.uk
Preferences
Session
No
No
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
Promatuk#lang
Registers our language selection to facilitate future browsin
www.promat.co.uk
Preferences
Session
No
No
N/A
Sinatuk#lang
Registers our language selection to facilitate future browsing
www.siniat.co.uk
Preferences
Session
No
No
N/A
Promatuk#persistedlang
The persisted Lang cookie retains the language locale of the user 9en)
www.promat.co.uk
Preferences
Session
No
No
N/A
Siniatuk#persistedlang
The persisted Lang cookie retains the language locale of the user 9en)
www.siniat.co.uk
Preferences
Session
No
No
N/A
CookieConsent
Visitor preferences
Stores the user's cookie consent state for the current domain
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Necessary
1 Year
No
Yes
https://www.cookiebot.com/en/cookie-declaration/
CookieConsentBulkTicket
Technical information
Preserves the visitor's session state across page requests.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Necessary
2 years from set/update
No
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
scWfmAntiCSRF
Prevents Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks where a malicious website can influence the interaction between a client browser and a web app that trusts the browser
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Necessary
Session
No
No
N/A
test_cookie
Statistical data
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
Session
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_ga_g1
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_ceg.s
Used by the service Crazy Egg to register where the visitor clicks on the website. The cookie enables the service to recognize the visitor on returning visits
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
3 months
Yes
Yes
https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy
_ceg.u
Used by the service Crazy Egg to register where the visitor clicks on the website. The cookie enables the service to recognize the visitor on returning visits
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
3 months
Yes
Yes
https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy
_ceir
Used by the service Crazy Egg to register where the visitor clicks on the website. The cookie enables the service to recognize the visitor on returning visits
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
5 years
Yes
Yes
https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy
Cookie name
Statistical Data
Used to monitor performance of the website. Helps improve the service we provide.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
Session
No
No
https://policies.google.com/privacy
collect
Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor’s device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://www.googletagmanager.com/gtm
ai_user
Used by Microsoft Application Insights software to collect statistical usage and telemetry information.
The cookie stores a unique identifier to recognize users on returning visits over time
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://az416426.vo.msecnd.net/scripts/a/ai.0.js
_ga
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
2 years
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_gat
Statistical Data
Detects how often the social sharing service, Add This, encounters the same user
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
13 month
Yes
Yes
https://s7.addthis.com
_utmb
Registers a timestamp with the exact time of when the user accessed the website as well as dates for the first and most recent visit. User by Google analytics
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
Session
No
No
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_utmc
Registers a timestamp with the exact time of when the user leaves the website.
Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
Session
No
No
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_utmz
Used by Google Analytics to collect data on where the user came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked and what search term was used.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
6 months
No
No
https://policies.google.com/privacy
_atuvc
This is associated with the Add This social sharing widget.
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
13 months
No
No
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
Cookie name
Category of information stored
Statistical Data
Geolocation, which is used to help providers determine how users who share information with each other are geographically located (state level)
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
13 months
No
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
Uid
Collects info on the user and his/her movement, such as timestamp for visit, most recently loaded pages and IP address. Used by social research network, Scorecard Research to analyse patters and carry out surveys to help us understand the customer preferences.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx
UIDR
Collects info on the user and his/her movement, such as timestamp for visit, most recently loaded pages and IP address. Used by social research network, Scorecard Research to analyse patters and carry out surveys to help us understand the customer preferences.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
2 years
Yes
Yes
https://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx
_utma
Collects data on the number of times a user has visited the website as well as dates for the first and most recent visit. Used by Google Analytics
www.promat.co.uk
Statistics
2 years
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
Cookie name
Category of information stored
Statistical Data
Collects information of the user and his/her movement, such as a timestamp for visits, most recently loaded pages and IP address.
The data is used by the Marketing research network, scorecard research, to analyse traffic, patterns and carry out surveys to help their clients better understand the customers preferences
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
2 years
Yes
Yes
https://www.scorecardresearch.com/privacy.aspx
ads/ga-audiences
Marketing Data
Used by Google AdWords ro re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitors online behaviour across websites
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://www.googletagmanager.com/gtm
ai_session
Marketing Data
DoubleClick by Google collects data to measure efficiency of viewed or clicked ads and shows targeted ads
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
ads/user-lists/#
Used by Google when a user visits a page on a website containing a remarketing tag. Google puts a cookie on the user’s device and adds the cookie to a ‘user list’. This is simply a collection of visitor cookies generated by one (or more) remarketing tags.
www.siniat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://www.googletagmanager.com/gtm
ssc
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to allow visitors to share our online content to social media sites.
www.promat.co.u
Marketing
13 months
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
xtc
RegistErs the user’s sharing of content via social media
Marketing Data
Ensures that the updated counter is displayed to the user if a page is shared with the social sharing service
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
_at.cww
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis
bcookie
Used by the social networking service, Linkedin, for tracking the use of embedded services.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
bscookie
Used by the social networking service, Linkedin, for tracking the use of embedded services
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
Cookie name
Category of information stored
Marketing Data
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to keep a record of parts of the site that has been visited in order to recommend other parts of the site
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://s7.addthis.com
Leo_auth_token
Used by the social networking service, Linkedin, for tracking the use of embedded services
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
lidc
Used by the social networking service, Linkedin, for tracking the use of embedded services
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
mus
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to store profile status.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
ouid
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis and is currently undocumented.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
Cookie name
Category of information stored
Marketing Data
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to allow visitors to share our online content to social media sites.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
13 months
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
sshs
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to allow visitors to share our online content to social media sites.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
13 months
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
vc
Used by the social sharing platform AddThis to allow visitors to share our online content to social media sites
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/
visit
Used by the social networking service, Linkedin, for tracking the use of the embedded services
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
2 years
Yes
Yes
https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-table
Cookie name
Category of information stored
User Tracking data
Registers a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
Tries to estimate the users' bandwidth on pages with integrated YouTube videos.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
179 days
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
IDE
Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user’s action after viewing o clicking one of the advertiser’s ads with the purpose of measuring the efficiency of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
1 year
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
PREF
Registers a unique ID that is used by Google to keep statistics of how the visitor uses YouTube videos across different websites.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
8 months
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
uuid2
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user’s device.
The ID is used for targeted ads
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
3 months
Yes
No
N/A
Cookie name
Profiling data
These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Persistent
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
GPS
Device location /ID tracking data
Registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.
www.siniat.co.uk
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
Session
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
NID
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
6 months
Yes
Yes
https://policies.google.com/privacy
TapAD_DID
Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc) is used by a user
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
2
months
Yes
Yes
https://www.tapad.com/privacy-policy
TapAD_TS
Used to determine what type of devices (smartphones, tablets, computers, TVs etc) is used by a user.
www.promat.co.uk
Marketing
months
Yes
Yes
https://www.tapad.com/privacy-policy
Additional information about specific cookies
Google Analytics: This Website uses Google Analytics, which is a web data analysis tool of Google Inc. (Google). Google Analytics uses cookies to help Us analyze how users use the Website.
Since we have activated the anonymization of IP-addresses transferre, Google will prior to such transfer truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address within Member States of the EEA. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on Website activity for Us and providing other services relating to Website activity and internet usage to Us. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html. Please note that on this Website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by “anonymizeIp” to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).
How to prevent cookies to be set
You may prevent cookies to be set by adjusting your browser accordingly. Indeed, most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about how to prevent cookies to be set, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
However, in such case, certain features of the Website may not work properly and some functionalities of the Website might no longer be available to you.
How to delete/deactivate cookies
In order to delete/deactivate all cookies set on your computer, the majority of web browsers allow you to disable completely the use of cookies, or to delete cookies created by specific domains/websites. To find out how to do it, please refer to your browser’s help page:
Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en
Internet Explorer: http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11-win-7
Firefox: http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences
Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US
Safari on IOS: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265
Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies
You can specifically prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) for any website you visit by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB.
You may [also] specifically refuse the use of Google Analytics on this Website by clicking on the following link. An opt-out cookie will be set on the computer, which prevents the future collection of your data when visiting this Website:
Disable Google Analytics: Click here to opt-out of Google Analytics
Share on social networks
We make use of a social plug-in to enable you to share Website’s information on Facebook or LinkedIn through “Share” buttons.
For data privacy reasons, we deliberately opted against utilizing direct social network plug-ins on our Website. Instead, we employ an alternative technical solution that allows you to decide whether to transmit data to the social network operators and when. Thus when you visit the Website, data are never automatically transmitted to a social network. Only when you actively click on the respective button yourself will your web browser connect to the servers of the social network, i.e. clicking on elements then clicking on the social network’s icon indicates your consent to your browser connecting to the servers of the social network and sending usage data to that social network operator, whether or not you are a subscriber of such social network.
We have no influence over the nature or scope of data that social networks may then gather. For information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, further processing and use of data by social networks and regarding your data privacy rights and relevant configuration settings, see the social networks’ respective data privacy advisories.
Links to third parties websites
On certain areas of this Website, We may provide links to third parties websites, which are not subject to this Privacy Notice. These links are provided as a convenience to you; however please be aware that We do not control such third parties or their websites and that those third parties will have a different privacy notice applying to information collected from you when you are on those third parties’ websites. We encourage you read the privacy notices of all websites carefully before providing personally identifiable information.
Storage duration
We will retain your Personal Data only as long as necessary for the fulfilment of the purposes described above or as required by law, or to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights
Security and confidentiality
We have implemented technical and organisational measures in accordance with standard industry practices to ensure an appropriate level of security of the Personal Data processed. Nevertheless, security requires efforts from all actors involved. We thus encourage you to contribute to these efforts by taking appropriate security measures yourself, including using strong passwords and keeping all user names and passwords (if any) confidential.
Children on the Website
This Website is not intended for or directed to children under 16. We do not knowingly collect any information from such individuals. If you believe your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us at marketing@etexbp.co.uk
Your rights
At any time, you may exercise your right to request access to or rectification of and, as the case may be, erasure of any Personal Data relating to you. You may also object to processing, or request a restriction of processing and benefit of a right to data portability (as the case may be), in compliance with applicable data protection law, by sending a signed request form with a copy of your ID card, passport or other proof of identity to marketing@etexbp.co.uk or in writing to Etex Building Performance Ltd, Gordano House, Marsh Lane, Easton in Gordano, Bristol, BS20 0NE
When applicable, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent made prior to such withdrawal.
As a data subject, you have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (in particular in the Member State of the European Union of your usual place of residence, your place of work or the place where the violation occurred) if you consider that the processing of Personal Data relating to you infringes the applicable legislation relating to data protection.
Data Protection Compliance Officer
Compliance Officer
Etex’s group Compliance Officer can be contacted at
complianceofficer@etexgroup.com with regard to all issues related to processing of your Personal Data and to the exercise of your rights under the applicable national and European legislation relating to data protection.
Effective date and changes
This Privacy Notice is in effect since 25th May 2018. We reserve the right, at Our complete discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. You should check back periodically at this page to read the most recent version of this Privacy Notice as your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you acknowledge these changes.
Thank you for visiting this Website.
Promat, Etex Building Performance Limited, Gordano House, Marsh Lane, Easton-in-Gordano, Bristol, BS20 ONE
This site uses cookies to provide you with a more responsive and personalised service.
By using this site you agree to our use of cookies.
Please read our cookie policy for more information on the cookies we use and how to delete or block them.
Accept
<![endif]-->
